

LUIS JOSÉ RADA CORDOBA

RPA DEVELOPER- INDUSTRIAL ING. WEB DEVELOPMENT STUDENT

PERSONAL PROFILE

Industrial engineer focused on the Logistics area and the technology industry. I have experience in logistics inventory control and RPA solutions software development. I am characterized by the constant interest in continuous learning and the correct understanding of processes for the generation of value.

SKILLS

- English level B2 conversational
- RPA: UiPath+Rocketbot,+Python
- Other tools: JavaScript+Css+Html

REFERENCES

JAIRO ALEXANDER QUICENO

Logistic Operation Coordinator at Comfenalco Antioquia

Contact Number: +57 313 637 8932

CONTACT ME



(+57 302 435 0904

✓ luis14rada@gmail.com

്ന്ന www.linkedin.com/in/luisradac

Medellín, Colombia

EDUCATION

- Industrial Engineer from the University of Medellín
- Subjects of the specialization in business logistics at the University of Medellin (6)
- Full Stack Web Development in Acámica Currently (html/Css/Javascript/NodeJS/Databases)

RELEVANT COURSEWORK AND CERTIFICATION

- Database Fundamentals Course, Platzi
- Python Programming Course, U de M Jun 2020
- RPA DEVELOPER ADVANCED UIPATH, UiPath Ago 2020
- Bot Builder Rocketbot Expert level 1, Rocketbot Oct 2020
- Data Analysis and Visualization Course with PowerBI, U de M Nov

WORK EXPERIENCE

CAJA DE COMPENSACIÓN COMFENALCO ANTIQUIA, INTERNSHIP IN LOGISTIC OPERATIONS AREA

DECEMBER 2019 - JULY 2020

- Extraction of purchasing information (period 2010-2019) from SAP platform. Cleaning, understanding and manipulation of information with PowerBI.
- Statistical analysis of information for inventory reduction through the use of ABC Classification and Exponential Smoothing Models
- A pre-feasibility proposal was generated and approved for inventory control at the departmental level

2NV SAS RPA DEVELOPER

JULY 2020 - CURRENTLY

- Active participation in the construction of documentation in a rpa process through the use of the Bizagi and draw.io tools
- Development of rpa solutions under agile scrum methodology managed through Microsoft Azure and the Git version controller. Development with Computer Vision and Databases are highlighted.